Guide to the Doris Duke Audiovisual Collection, 1919-2012 and undated RL.10005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio, 1923-1989
  - Phonodiscs, 1934-1989; 198 items
    - Fats Waller Favorites - Victor Musical Smart Set - "Ain't Misbehavin'" / "Hold Tight", 1937
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0130)
    - Fats Waller Favorites - Victor Musical Smart Set - "I Can't Give You Anything But Love, Baby" / "The Joint Is Jumpin'", 1937
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0131)
    - Fats Waller Favorites - Victor Musical Smart Set - "Two Sleepy People" /"The Minor Drag", 1937
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0132)
    - Rainbow Trio. A Perfect Lady / My Buddy, 1937 August 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0037_Perfect_Lady_My_Buddy_01; RL10005-PD-0037_Perfect_Lady_My_Buddy_02)
      Instrumental only, traditional Hawaiian music. Sounds similar to recordings in "Organ Treasures".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0037)
    - Rainbow Trio. Aloha Sunset Land / At Dawning, 1937 August 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0038_Aloha_Sunset_Land_Dawning_01; RL10005-PD-0038_Aloha_Sunset_Land_Dawning_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0038)
    - Rainbow Trio. Memory Lane / Hawaiian Paradise, 1937 August 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0039_Memory_Paradise_01; RL10005-PD-0039_Memory_Paradise_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0039)
    - Organ Treasures. Akahi Hoi / Nani Wale Lihue, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0029_Akahi_Hoi_Nani_Wale_01; RL10005-PD-0029_Akahi_Hoi_Nani_Wale_02)
      Instrumental only, traditional Hawaiian music.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0029)
    - Organ Treasures. Lei Poni Moi / Aloha No Au I Ko Maka, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0030_Lei_Poni_Aloha_No_01; RL10005-PD-0030_Lei_Poni_Aloha_No_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0030)
    - Organ Treasures. King's Serenade / Love Wreaths, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0031_Kings_Serenade_Love_Wreath_01; RL10005-PD-0031_Kings_Serenade_Love_Wreath_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0031)
    - Organ Treasures. Maikai Waipio, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0032_Maikai_Waipio_01)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0032)
    - Organ Treasures. Makaluapua / Aloha Oe, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0033_Makaluapua_Aloha_Oe_01; RL10005-PD-0033_Makaluapua_Aloha_Oe_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0033)
    - Organ Treasures. Mikioi / Mai Poina Oe La'u, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0034_Mikioi_Mai_Poina_Oe_Lau_01; RL10005-PD-0034_Mikioi_Mai_Poina_Oe_Lau_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0034)
    - Organ Treasures. Pulupe Nei lli I Ke Anu / Waialae, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0035_Pulupe Nei lli I Ke Anu, Waialae_01; RL10005-PD-0035_Pulupe Nei lli I Ke Anu, Waialae_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0035)
    - Organ Treasures. Poli Pumehana / Palama, 1937 August 9 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0036_Poli_Pumehana_Palama_01; RL10005-PD-0036_Poli_Pumehana_Palama_02)
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0036)
    - Fats Waller and his Rhythm. "Honeysuckle Rose" / "Blue, Turning Grey Over You", circa 1937
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0133)
    - Fats Waller and his Rhythm. "Honeysuckle Rose" / "Blue, Turning Grey Over You", circa 1937
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0134)
    - Various artists including Louis, Ann, Johnny, Bernice, David, Paoa, Kailani, and Hapuki., 1938 January 14 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0061_Aloha_Oh_Unknown_01; RL10005-PD-0061_Aloha_Oh_Unknown_02)
      Side 1 of album consists of 5 tracks featuring a variety of singers/singing groups. Sing primarily Hawaiian songs. Side 2 has 3 tracks again with a variety of songs. Last song is Aloha 'Oe.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0061)
    - Various artists including Sam, Bill, Louis Berin, 1938 January 14 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0062_Wahine_Hui_E2_Sweet_Little_01; RL10005-PD-0062_Wahine_Hui_E2_Sweet_Little_02)
      Both sides consist of recordings of music. All recordings begin and end abruptly. Overall sound is faint and frequently skips and therefore difficult to discern singers and songs.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 16, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0062)
    - Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra. I'll Never Smile Again / Marcheta, 1940
      Alternate title given in Spanish: "Jamás Reiré Otra Vez." Side A vocal refrain by Frank Sinatra and the Pied Pipers; this is apparently Sinatra's first hit single.
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0027)
    - Side 1: Laughing on the Outside, Recorder: Virginia Hays; Side 2: [Untitled], 1946 November 25 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0010_Unknown_CTOP10_01; RL10005-PD-0010_Unknown_CTOP10_02)
      First track presumably Virginia Hays singing "Laughing on the Outside" accompanied by piano. Second track is identical, although the track is barely audible.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0010)
    - Alex Haas and His Budapest Gypsy Ensemble. Magyar Gipsy Melodies - I would like to pick lilacs in a May night, 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0101)
    - Alex Haas and His Budapest Gypsy Ensemble. Magyar Gipsy Melodies - Calmly flows the river Maros, 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0102)
    - Alex Haas and His Budapest Gypsy Ensemble. Magyar Gipsy Melodies - Applaud and enjoy yourself, 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0103)
    - KGU Radio Artists, Honolulu. "The Story of James Buchanan Duke", Parts 1 & 2 of 4, 1949 November 22 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0106_Honolulu_1_4_1; RL10005-PD-0106_Honolulu_1_4_2)
      "The Story of James Buchanan Duke" is narrated and "acted" on radio by an assortment of actors.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0106)
    - KGU Radio Artists, Honolulu. "The Story of James Buchanan Duke", Parts 3 & 4 of 4, 1949 November 22 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0107_Honolulu_1_4_3; RL10005-PD-0107_Honolulu_1_4_4)
      "The Story of James Buchanan Duke" is narrated and "acted" on radio by an assortment of actors. Ends with a female narrator summarizing the story and comparing it to the sugar industry in Hawaii. Interviews James N. Orrick, manager of Ever Plantation a sugar plantation in Hawaii.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0107)
    - Old Rockin' Chair's Got Me, 1949 September 19 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0073_Old_Rockin_Chairs_01)
      Presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing "Old Rockin' Chair's Got Me".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0073)
    - The Jazz Scene. The Duke Ellington Sides, circa 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0153)
    - The Jazz Scene. The Lester Young Side / The Coleman Hawkins Side, circa 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0154)
    - The Jazz Scene. The Ralph Burns Side / The George Handy Side, circa 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0155)
    - The Jazz Scene. The Charlie Parker Side / The Willie Smith Side, circa 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0156)
    - The Jazz Scene. The Manchito Side / The Bud Powell Side, circa 1949
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0157)
    - Frank J. Hale presents The World Premiere Of "The Princess". The Princess, Acts I and III, circa 1950s
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0160)
    - George Kainapau with Danny Stewart's Hawaiians/George Kainapau with Sam Koki and His Paradise Islanders. Kealoha/E Kuu Lei, 1951
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0158)
    - Ella Fitzgerald. Jazz with Jackson, 1953 December 12 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0112_Jazz_With_Jackson_1_3_01; RL10005-PD-0112_Jazz_With_Jackson_1_3_02)
      Side 1 opens with band rehearsing "Fascinating Rhythm" and then ends abruptly. Man (presumably Calvin Jackson) describes Gershwin and the song and how it's going to be played. Band rehearses entire song. Jackson then describes the next song to be rehearsed, "S'Wonderful" by quartet consisting of Don McFadden on bass, Peter Appleyard on vibes, Jack McCrea on drums (and Calvin on piano). Side 2 Jackson announces they are going "back to Big Band" and describes "Love Walked In" and discusses the arrangement. Quartet plays song.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0112)
    - Ella Fitzgerald. Jazz with Jackson, 1953 December 12 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0113_Jazz_With_Jackson_1_3_03)
      Side 3 has Calvin Jackson announcing that "we have a real change of pace for you". Describes the movie "Flying Down to Rio" and the hit song "Carioca". Describes arrangement and then band plays song. Jackson then talks to band members and then plays Vincent Youman's song "Sometimes I'm Happy". After song talks to band members, start playing unknown song and song fades out.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0113)
    - Percy Faith and Mitch Miller. Music Until Midnight, 1954
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0075)
    - Eddie Lund and his Tahitians. Rendezvous in Tahiti, 1954
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0159)
    - U[?] Kolitsch. Estrellita (To Mrs. Doris Duke Cromwell respectfully dedicated U[?] Kolitsch), 1954 April 4
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0116)
    - Vincent Youmans?, 1954 January 13
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0126)
    - Vincent Youmans?, 1954 January 13
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0127)
    - Duke Ellington and His Orchestra. A Drum is a Woman, 1956
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0074)
    - Fats Waller and his Rhythm. Handful of Keys, 1957
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0135)
    - Elvis Presley with The Jordanaires. I Need You So, Have I Told You Lately That I Love You/Blueberry Hill, Is It So Strange, 1957
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0152)
    - Joe Castro. Lush Life, 1960 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0109_Lush_Life_01; RL10005-PD-0109_Lush_Life_02)
      Songs are instrumental only. Very different style from RL10005-PD-0108 as piano is backed up by orchestra and back up singers for several of the songs.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0109)
    - Kitty White. Kitty White, circa 1960s (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0125_Visit_Me_01; RL10005-PD-0125_Visit_Me_02)
      Promotional copy, not for sale. This was Kitty White's Clover debut album. Includes album jacket.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0125)
    - Tori Savage and the Minks. Tell Me/You Thought You Hurt Me, circa 1960s
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0140)
    - Tori Savage and the Minks. Tell Me/You Thought You Hurt Me, circa 1960s
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0141)
    - Tori Savage and the Minks. Tell Me/You Thought You Hurt Me, circa 1960s
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0142)
    - Kitty White. Visit Me, Summer In The City, My Kind Of Guy, Happiness Is A Thing Called Joe, So Many Beautiful Men, Do It Again, Call Me Darling/Disenchanted Lady, Oh, For Just A Chance To Love You, Bosa Nova All The Way, Say It Isn't So, Just In Time, Moo, circa 1960s
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0161)
    - Rev. Lawrence Roberts and the Angelic Choir of the First Baptist Church, Nutley, NJ. The Angelic Choir, 1961
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0094)
    - Petula Clark. Downtown/You'd Better Love Me, 1964
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0151)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir. Volume 5: Give Me My Flowers, 1965
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0083)
    - Evangelist Rosie Wallace and the First Church of Love, Faith and Deliverance Choir. God Cares., 1966
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0082)
    - Johnny Mercer, Nelson Riddle, Lindsay Crosby voice to be dubbed over. Sailing Down the Chesapeake Bay, circa 1966 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0117_Sailing_Down_JM_01)
      Dub record. Johnny Mercer and Nelson Riddle provide orchestra and some singing. Expectation that Lindsay Crosby's voice would be overdubbed. George Jay Associates attempted to sell it to Clover Record in 1966.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0117)
    - Nelson Riddle, Lindsay Crosby. Sailing Down the Chesapeake Bay/Going Steady With a Memory, circa 1966 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0118_Sailing_Down_NR_Going_Steady_01; RL10005-PD-0118_Sailing_Down_NR_Going_Steady_02)
      Side 1 is music track only. Side 2 is Lindsay Crosby singing "Going Steady with a Memory" backed up by Nelson Riddle Orchestra.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0118)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir. Volume 8 - Part 1, 1968
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0085)
    - Aretha Franklin. Prove It /Chain of Fools, 1968
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0150)
    - Rev. Lawrence Roberts Presents Dorothy Norwood and the Angelic Choir. Dorothy Norwood and the Angelic Choir, circa 1968
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0099)
    - James Cleveland with the Angelic Choir and the Cleveland Singers. Merry Christmas, 1969
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0088)
    - Reverend Robert J. Lucas and His Christian Temple Choir. The King and I, 1969
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0093)
    - Niny Ruffini. "Pace Mio Dio", "Tu che di gel sei cinta" / Ebben N'andro Lontana, 1969 July 29
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0121)
    - Ray Charles. That Thing Called Love/Laughin and Clownin, 1970
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0147)
    - Aretha Franklin. Bridge Over Troubled Water/Brand New Me, 1971
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0148)
    - Cissy Houston. Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow / Midnight Train to Georgia, 1972
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0180)
    - James Cleveland Presents The Charles Fold Singers of Cincinnati, Ohio. Jesus is the Best Thing That Ever Happened to Me., 1975
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0090)
    - James Cleveland Presents The Charles Fold Singers of Cincinnati, Ohio. Jesus is the Best Thing That Ever Happened to Me., 1975
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0091)
    - Orson Welles, Leonard Bernstein. The Airborne Symphony, 1976
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0079)
    - Art Hodes. Music Until Midnight Jacket, 1977
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0076)
    - George Mgrdichian. The New Sounds of the Middle East, 1986
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0077)
    - George Mgrdichian. George Mgrdichian on the Oud, 1986
      - Phonodisc (Box 17, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0078)
    - Bishop Jeff Banks & Revival Temple Mass Choir. The Storm is Over, 1989
      - Phonodisc (Box 18, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0081)
    - In envelope marked "Miss Doris", undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0001_Miss_Doris_Fla_b_1_01; RL10005-PD-0001_Miss_Doris_Fla_b_1_02)
      Presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing. First track "There'll Be Some Changes Made"; second track "Too Marvelous for Words".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0001)
    - In envelope marked "Miss Doris", undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0002_Miss_Doris_F2_01)
      Presumably Doris Duke playing piano and singing. Begins playing and singing "Too Marvelous for Words" and then stops after a couple of bars. Sings "There'll Be Some Changes Made".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0002)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0003_Unknown_J1_01; RL10005-PD-0003_Unknown_J1_02)
      Unknown female singer accompanied by piano. First track "Can't Take That Away from Me"; second track "Ain't Misbehavin'".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0003)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0004_Unknown_J2_01)
      Unknown female singer accompanied by piano. Begins singing "Can't Take That Away from Me" and ends abruptly.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0004)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0005_Unknown_DD1_01)
      Unknown female singer accompanied by piano (likely the same singer as in RL10005-PD-0004). Song title is unknown.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0005)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0006_Unknown_CTOP2_01; RL10005-PD-0006_Unknown_CTOP2_02)
      Both songs are presumably traditional Hawaiian music, however titles are unknown. First track is instrumental only; second track includes male singers accompanied by background instrumentals.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0006)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0007_Unknown_CTOP6_01)
      Genre and title is unknown. Instrumental only (piano and slide(?) guitar). At end of track man states "track by Jimmy Robb and David Sahili[?]".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0007)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0008_Unknown_CTOP7_01; RL10005-PD-0008_Unknown_CTOP7_02)
      Presumably Doris Duke singing accompanied by unknown pianist. First track is "Dinah" and unknown man joins in at the end of the song. Second track begins by woman (presumably Doris Duke) stating that recorder is on. Piano music begins and stops and then Doris and man have brief conversation. Second song title unknown; primarily piano only, however Doris hums and speaks throughout. Third track is severely garbled. Song and singer unrecognizable.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0008)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0009_Unknown_CTOP9_01; RL10005-PD-0009_Unknown_CTOP9_02)
      First track begins with man speaking into the mic, presumably testing out the track equipment (talking to another man named "Dave"). Other people and low music can be heard in the background. Instrumental music begins; sounds very similar to music in RL10005-PD-0007. Midway through song same man states "Ladies and gentleman, that is the Kailani Lahi Lahi Orchestra..." (Kailani Lahi Lahi was Doris Duke's nickname). Second track, same man states "Ladies and gentlemen you are now about to enjoy the Kailani Lahi Lahi orchestra making mucho funny noises. Proceed orchestra." Instrumental with slide guitar, ukulele. Song unknown, although sounds like traditional Hawaiian music.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0009)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0011_Unknown_CTOP11_01; RL10005-PD-0011_Unknown_CTOP11_02)
      First track is Bernice Kahanamoku singing "Dream of Old Hawaii". She is accompanied by Sam Kahanamoku, Melvin (?), and Bill Kahanamoku. Second track is Sam, Melvin, and Bill singing a native Hawaiian song (title unknown).Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0011)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0012_Unknown_CTOP12_01; RL10005-PD-0012_Unknown_CTOP12_02)
      Unknown man announces that the "next number will be a piano solo played by [garbled] Robb". Song unknown as it is very difficult to hear the instrumental. Second track is "[?] Paradise" sung by Sam Kahanamoku. Difficult to hear as faint and garbled.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0012)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0013_Unknown_CTOP16_01; RL10005-PD-0013_Unknown_CTOP16_02)
      First track, unknown man announces "Good evening. We're going to dedicate this song to Mr. Fred Cady from his beloved wife Vi. Here we go, listen everybody." Unknown man and woman sing "Stormy Weather" accompanied by guitar. Other people commenting in background. The couple makes a mistake, people laugh, track ends. Same man and woman sing "My Country 'Tis of Thee" accompanied by guitar. Second track unknown man announces "Hello everybody, how you are? [laughs] First, I'm going to dedicate this song to Bijou. Now David will you play so I can sang this song? [laughter] I'm gonna sang one song." Sings "Maybe" accompanied by slide guitar. Abruptly ends, switches to piano solo; song is unknown.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 15, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0013)
    - [Untitled], undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0014_Unknown_CTOP14_01; RL10005-PD-0014_Unknown_CTOP14_02)